<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>2.01</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 2.0.1.17 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>NDW Ltd</Company_Name>
		<Address_1>NDW House</Address_1>
		<Address_2 />
		<City_Town>Sandiacre</City_Town>
		<State_Province>NOTTS</State_Province>
		<Zip_Postal_Code>NG9 6OX</Zip_Postal_Code>
		<Country>England</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Ted</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Ferenc</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>support@ndrw.co.uk</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Ted</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Ferenc</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>support@ndrw.co.uk</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>sales@ndrw.co.uk</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>support@ndrw.co.uk</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>support@ndrw.co.uk</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone>+44(0)7904346850</Sales_Phone>
			<Support_Phone>+44(0)7904346850</Support_Phone>
			<General_Phone>+44(0)7904346850</General_Phone>
			<Fax_Phone />
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>JPGAvi</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.07.0.68</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>11</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>05</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2006</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>29.99</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x,Windows2000,WinXP,Windows2003</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info />
		<Program_Specific_Category>Graphics</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class />
		<Program_Categories>Multi Media</Program_Categories>
		<Program_System_Requirements>Default Windows system</Program_System_Requirements>
		<Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
		<Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
		<Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
		<File_Info>
			<Filename_Versioned>jpgav107.zip</Filename_Versioned>
			<Filename_Previous>jpgav106.zip</Filename_Previous>
			<Filename_Generic>jpgavi.zip</Filename_Generic>
			<Filename_Long>jpgavi.zip</Filename_Long>
			<File_Size_Bytes>1193023</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>1165</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>1.14</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count>30</Expire_Count>
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>JPGAvi,JPGVideo,AVI, NDW,NDRW,DIVX,Video,Multimedia,Graphics,Codec</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>JPGAvi converts bitmap into multimedia files.</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>JPGAvi creates a video, (AVI) file from a series, or individual,  bitmap files.</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>JPGAvi creates a video, animation/slide show,  (AVI) file from a series, or individual,  bitmap files.  These can be viewed as a video file or used to insert still frames into a video sequence. Also a sound file can be attached to the video.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>JPGAvi creates a video,  (AVI) file from a series, or individual,  bitmap files. These can be viewed as a video file or used to insert still frames into a video sequence. One of JPGAvi's main uses is to convert still pictures into an AVI file, so they can be used when editing a video sequence. The video file can contains the names of each bitmap, so  if a web cam is used to take photographs every few seconds, it becomes very easy to find a frame.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>JPGAvi creates a video, animation, (AVI) file from a series, or individual,  bitmap files, also a  sound file can be attached to the video..  These can be viewed as a video file or used to insert still frames into a video sequence. One of JPGAvi's main uses is to convert still pictures into an AVI file, so they can be used when editing a video sequence. A slide show option is also built in. The video file can contains the names of each bitmap, so  if a web cam is used to take photographs every few seconds, it becomes very easy to find a frame. The shareware version writes the text "JPGAvi Shareware Version" to each frame, there is a 30 day time limit to it's usage also.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk/shareware/jpgavi/purchase/index.html</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk/shareware/jpgavi/images/screenshot.gif</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk/shareware/jpgavi/images/progicon.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk/download/shareware/jpgavi/pad_file.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.ndrw.co.uk/download/shareware/jpgavi/jpgavi.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL />
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions />
		<EULA>End-user and distribution license agreement.

Except where otherwise noted, all of the documentation and software included in 
the JPGAvi package is Copyrighted by Mr. T. Ferenc NDW Ltd. 

Copyright (c) 2002 - 2005 Mr. T. Ferenc NDW Ltd. All rights reserved. 

This software is provided "as-is," without any express or implied warranty. In 
no event shall the author, nor NDW Ltd., be held liable for any damages arising 
from the use of this software. 

JPGAvi may not be rented or leased, but the user may freely evaluate and 
distribute JPGAvi, a small charge or fee may be charged for the physical act of 
transferring a copy. If after 30 days you wish to continue using JPGAvi please 
register it, although you may use it indefinitely without registering. 

There will be no refund of this fee, it is up to the user to evaluate the 
software during the trial period to ensure it is suitable for their 
requirements. 

This software may be distributed on online services, bulletin boards, or other 
electronic media, and on CD-ROM, disk, or other physical media as long as the 
distribution package is not modified. 

To register the registration form must be completed, on line, and the 
registration fee paid at the authorised registration site. See the registration 
box in JPGAvi for details. 

NDW reserve the right not to supply replacement keycodes, if a customer has lost 
their copy unless written proof of purchase is supplied.

Once registered, the user is granted a non-exclusive license to use JPGAvi on 
one computer, for any legal purpose, at a time. Non commercial users may install 
JPGAvi on any number of computers, that are owned by the registered user, at 
their home, corporate users must purchase a site license, email sales@ndrw.co.uk 
for details. 

The user must not clone, emulate, or in any way reverse engineer, rent, lease, 
sell, or modify the program and supplied files (help, examples, pre-sets etc.) 
The user may not de-compile, reverse engineer, disassemble or otherwise reduce 
this software to a human perceivable form. The user may not modify, rent or sell 
for profit this software, or create derivative works based upon this software. 

The user must not alter this software in any way, including changing or removing 
any messages or windows. 

NDW Ltd. reserve the right to email you when a new version of JPGAvi has been 
produced, we will NOT use your email address for any other purpose.

If you do not agree with this license you must delete JPGAvi and all associated 
files and discontinue to use it. 

In the event of any dispute the law in England and Wales will prevail. 

JPGAvi (c) 2002 - 2005  Mr. T. Ferenc NDW Ltd.
http://www.ndrw.co.uk
NDW Ltd. is registered in England and Wales No. 3749122</EULA>
	</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
